http://www.csmtube.com/privacy-policy.html

Production
Stainless Steel TubeTechnical specificationsTechnical Reference StandardsTest and ControlsRoHS and REACH Declaration
Applications
Heat ExchangersFood and BeverageHeating ElementsAutomotiveElectric water heaterSolar CollectorsTube ManipulationHeater Appliances
Production
Stainless Steel TubeTechnical specificationsTechnical Reference StandardsTest and ControlsRoHS and REACH Declaration
Applications
Heat ExchangersFood and BeverageHeating ElementsAutomotiveElectric water heaterSolar CollectorsTube ManipulationHeater Appliances
News
Contact Us
ContactsCommercial RequestsWork with us
HomePrivacy policy
INFORMATION NOTICE CONCERNING THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA
CSM TUBE spa (hereinafter “Company”) provides this information notice pursuant and for the effects of art. 13 of (EU) Regulation 2016/679 (hereinafter “GDPR”) on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data in order to inform you of the purposes and methods of processing of the personal data that you may disclose while browsing this website (hereinafter “Site”).
We would like to point out that this information notice refers solely to the Site and not to third-party websites that the User may reach via links herein.
CATEGORIES OF PROCESSED DATABrowsing dataThe IT systems and the software procedures that are used for operating this website acquire, in their normal operation, certain personal data, the transmission of which is inherent in the use of Internet communication protocols. This information is not collected to be associated with identified data subjects but may, by its very nature, through processing and association with data held by third parties, allow the users to be identified. This category of data includes, for example, the IP addresses or domain names of the computers used by users who connect to the site, the URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) addresses of the requested resources, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code that indicates the status of the reply given by the server (success, error, etc.) and other parameters related to the user’s operating system and IT environment. These data are used for the sole purpose of retrieving anonymous statistical information on the use of the website and to monitor its correct operation, and are deleted immediately after processing.
Data provided intentionally by the UserOptional, express and intentional sending of e-mail to the addresses indicated in the Site results in the subsequent acquisition of the sender’s address necessary to reply to the requests, as well as of other personal data contained in the message. Specific summary information notices are also contained or displayed in the sections of the Site that are arranged for particular services on request and subject, if required, to the consent of the data subject.
CookiesIn accordance with the Decree of the Italian Data Protection Authority no. 229 of 8 May 2014 “Simplified Arrangements to Provide Information and Obtain Consent Regarding Cookies”, the Company would like to inform users on the use of navigation cookies on this Site. We would like to point out that this information notice refers solely to the Site and not to third-party websites that the User may reach via links herein.
What are cookies?A cookie is a small file sent to the browser in use and stored on your device when you visit a website such as csmtube.com. Cookies assure efficient operation of the Site and improve its performance, provide the owner of the Site with information for statistical or advertising purposes, mainly to personalise your browsing experience by remembering your preferences. The Site uses various types of first-party cookies prepared and managed by CSM TUBE spa and third-party cookies (prepared and managed by third parties on the basis of their own privacy policies and not under the control of CSM TUBE spa): please see the table below for explanations
TYPE OF COOKIES
FUNCTION
technical cookies (session or navigation)
They assure normal navigation and use of the website and are, therefore, intended to make navigation of the site functional and optimise it.
functionality cookies
They are strictly necessary to provide services expressly requested by the user.
first-party analytics cookies
They are used and created only by CSM TUBE spa, to collect anonymous information in aggregated form on the number of users and on how they visit the site.
third-party analytics cookies (e.g. Google Analytics)
CSM TUBE spa has adopted suitable tools to ensure that processing with these cookies is performed only for statistical purposes.
Enabling and disabling cookies from the Browser.
The majority of browsers is configured to accept, control or possibly disable cookies through the settings. Please remember, however, that disabling navigation or functional cookies may result in unsatisfactory operation of the site and/or limit the service we offer.
Please find below the links to manage cookies from the following browsers:Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/windows7/block-enable-or-allow-cookiesSafari: http://support.apple.com/kb/PH19255Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/a nswer/95647?hl=it-IT&hlrm=fr&hlrm=en
PURPOSE AND LEGAL BASIS OF THE PROCESSING, NATURE OF THE PROVISION OF DATA AND CONSEQUENCES IN THE EVENT OF REFUSALThe Company shall process the data to support navigation and provide any services that have been requested with the forms provided on the Site for this purpose. Aside from the information provided on navigation data and technical cookies, the sections of the Site contain, for particular services, requests for the provision of personal data for the purposes mentioned in the respective information notices; failure to provide them may make it impossible to obtain the service requested.
DATA RETENTION PERIODThe personal data that are collected through use of the Site are processed for the time strictly necessary to achieve the objectives for which they were collected or for any additional time that may have been set by the applicable regulations.
For more information, please see the information notices prepared for particular services.
SCOPE OF DISCLOSURE OF THE DATA AND CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTSSolely for the purposes specified above, all data collected and processed may be disclosed to employees who are authorised to perform processing by virtue of their respective tasks and to external entities to whom it may be necessary to disclose the data. Such recipients, should they process data on behalf of the Company, shall be appointed data processors with a specific contract or other legal deed.
For more information, please see the information notices prepared for particular services.
TRANSFER OF DATA TO ANOTHER COUNTRY AND/OR AN INTERNATIONAL ORGANISATIONThe personal data shall not be transferred to non-EU Countries. RIGHTS OF THE DATA SUBJECTSThe data subjects have the right (pursuant to articles 15-22 of the GDPR) to request from the Company access to their personal data and to rectify them if they are incorrect, erase them or restrict their processing if the conditions are met, as well as obtain the portability of the data they have provided only if they are subject to processing by automated means based on consent or on the contract. The data subjects also have the right to revoke the consent granted for the purposes of processing that require it, without prejudice to the lawfulness of the processing performed until the time of revocation; they also have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority, the Italian Data Protection Authority.
For more information, please see the information notices prepared for particular services.
Parties of the processingThe controller of the personal data is CSM TUBE spa who may be contacted in that capacity by sending a written request to CSM TUBE spa with registered office in Cimavilla di Codognè (TV), 60 Via del Lavoro, or by sending an e-mail to the address amministrazione.tube@csmtube.com.
Last update: July 2018.
This Information Notice may be amended. You are, therefore, advised to check this web page regularly and to take into account the most up-to-date version of the information notice contained therein
Global Presence
Italy
more
Brasil
more
USA
more
CSM Transforming
